argosyu.edu 2007-07-30

# Argosy University: Privacy Policy & Terms

Argosy University is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. We want you to understand what kinds of information we gather from you, how this information is used and protected, and how you can control its use. This statement discloses the privacy practices of Argosy University's Web site. By using this Web site, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Any changes in our Privacy Policy will be communicated in this page so please check back from time to time.

## Who May Use this Web site

Argosy University's Web site is not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person we know to be under the age of 13 and instruct users under 13 not to send us any information for collection on the this Web site. Argosy University's Web site is designed for users from the United States. Users from other countries are advised not to disclose personal information to Argosy University unless they consent to having their information used as set forth in this Web site's Privacy Policy rather than under the law of user's home country. You transmit data to a server located in Pennsylvania subject to United States and Pennsylvania law. You should not send any personal information to Argosy University's Web site unless you agree to be bound by this privacy policy and by United States and Pennsylvania law.

## Information Collected

In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our Web site tracking software collects the domain names but not the email addresses of visitors. Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you but is used to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site and the pages viewed. We use this information to measure the use of the site and improve the content delivered on the site. In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our Web site tracking software collects the domain names but not the email addresses of visitors. Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you but is used to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site and the pages viewed. We use this information to measure the use of the site and improve the content delivered on the site.

When you make a request for further information from Argosy University, you will be asked to provide certain contact information that will be collected and used for the purpose of responding to your request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone number or email address.

When you make a request for further information and provide Argosy University with your personal contact information, it will be collected and used for the purpose of responding to your specific requests. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you except as set forth in this Web site.

## How Your Information is Used

We utilize "cookies" on this Web site. Cookies are small files that we send to and store on your computer so that we may recognize it as a unique machine the next time you visit Argosy University's Web site. Unless you specify that you would prefer not to hear from us, we may also use the information you provide to Argosy University's Web site to contact you, or to have a company that works for us contact you. You may have these communications terminated if you give us notice. This likely will take four to six weeks from the time you give us notice.

## Your Choices Regarding Use of Your Personal Information

You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of Argosy University's Web site features. You also can add or update certain information that you send to us. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us or if you wish to check your information, please e-mail us at: [auwebmaster@edmc.edu](mailto:%20auwebmaster@edmc.edu).

## Access to Your Information

In the event that Argosy University and some of our assets or assets of our parent are sold or transferred or used as security, the information collected on our Web sites, including this Web site, may be transferred to third parties as part of that transaction. Argosy University may also provide information or provide access to information to any of our affiliated businesses or to our business partners.

Argosy University may use your contact information to reply to you and send information to you. Argosy University does not intend to reveal individually identifiable information to third parties except in the manner stated in the Privacy Policy. Argosy University will provide aggregated information received from you to third parties. Argosy University takes commercially reasonable precautions to prevent the aggregated information provided to third parties from including significant individually identifiable information.

If Argosy University is requested by law enforcement officials or judicial authorities to provide information on individuals, Argosy University may, without your consent, provide such information. In matters involving claims of personal or public safety or in litigation where the data is pertinent, Argosy University may use or disclose your personal information without your consent or court process.

## Will Your Information Be Secure?

Argosy University recognizes that you may be concerned about the security of your personal information, and we are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of this Web site. Even with such technology, no Web site is 100 percent secure. We will take reasonable measures which we believe are appropriate to protect your information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third parties to whom we may transfer your information take comparable steps to protect that security.

If you use this Web site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your access information and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your password.

We are the owner of data you supply to us.

## Information-Sharing Disclosure Request

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request one Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure per year, which will identify the third parties with whom Argosy University or any of its affiliates has shared the information we have collected from you. You may request the Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure by writing to us at: Argosy University, Two First National Plaza, 20 South Clark Street, 28th Floor, Chicago, IL 60603. You may also send us your Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure request via e-mail at [auwebmaster@edmc.edu](mailto:%20auwebmaster@edmc.edu) or by telephone at (toll-free) 1.800.377.0617. We will respond to your request for a Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure within 30 days of receipt.

## Our Privacy Policy and Outside Links

Our Privacy Policy only applies to the various Argosy University Web sites including this Web site. Our Web sites contain links to sites outside our control. Please be aware that these sites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices that may differ from our Privacy Policy. Remember to consult that Web site's own privacy policy, as once you are outside any of Argosy University's Web sites, any information you submit is no longer within our control.

## Questions Regarding Our Privacy Policy

If you have questions concerning our privacy practices, contact us at:

Privacy Administrator, Argosy University, 210 Sixth Avenue, Pittsburgh, PA 15222; FAX: (412) 995-7295; E-mail: [auwebmaster@edmc.edu](mailto:%20auwebmaster@edmc.edu).

## Consent of Non-U.S. Residents to be Bound by U.S. Law

This site is located in the United States and collection of personal information on this site is governed by United States law. You may not send us personal information unless you agree that your information will be stored, accessed, disclosed, processed and used in accordance with U.S. privacy laws and practices and in accordance with the Privacy Policy posted on this Web site. The laws that apply to this Web site and which govern our privacy and security practices may be different from the laws in your home country. DO NOT USE THIS WEB SITE UNLESS YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE LAWS OF THE UNITED STATES. If you choose to send us personal information, you have acknowledged, accepted, and agreed to the application of U.S. law. If you have questions about how your personal information will be processed on this Web site, please contact: [auwebmaster@edmc.edu](mailto:%20auwebmaster@edmc.edu).
